C+
C-plus?
还是体育
In gym?
爸
Dad.
哈  亲爱的戴个哨子的父亲大人
Ha! Loving father man who wears the whistle.
如果你不能让我的平均分变得好看些  我就永远都致不了毕业辞了
If I don't keep my perfect G.P.A., I will never be valedictorian.
而且我在机器人社里牛皮吹得老大
And I have been talking a lot of smack in robotics club.
所以还造了个会吹牛大吹特吹的机器人
So has the smack-talking robot I built.
抱歉了  儿子  但是我必须要给你打低分
Sorry, son, but I had to mark you down
因为你没能在 35 秒内完成折返跑
because you didn't finish your shuttle run in under 35 seconds.
35 秒  爸爸  那是不可能的
35 seconds? Daddy, that's impossible.
噢  是吗
Oh, yeah?
嘿  迪吉
Hey, Diggie.
你跑一趟折返跑看看
We're go for shuttle run.
现在开始计时
Timer starts now.
如果你想要的话  可以让你重考
If you want, I can give you a retest,
但你只能有一次机会
but you're only going to get one shot at it.
你的意思是我唯一能保证毕业的方法
You're telling me the only way I'm going to be valedictorian
就是像只蟑螂一样发疯的在体育馆里来回跑
is if I scurry across the gym floor like a jock-roach.
我又不是定规则的人  孩子
I don't make the rules, son.
我只是负责吹哨的
I just blow the whistle.
同时  我还教你们生理课
Also, I teach health class.
所以一旦你们对自己青春期的变化有什么疑问
So if you have any questions about your changing body,
我的门随时为你们敞开
my door is always open.
算了吧  还是把门关了得了
Yeah, let's keep that door closed.
完成了
Done!
折返跑跑得不错啊  迪吉
Nice shuttle run, Diggie.
28.7 秒
28.7 seconds.
我认为这是最好成绩了  孩子
I don't think any less of you, son.
嘿
Hey!
迪吉
Diggie.
我最爱的校队运动员
My favorite varsity athlete
也是唯一一个从不打击贬低我的家伙
and the only one who has never purpled my nurples.
我需要你帮个忙
I need a favor.
我必须在 35 秒内跑完折返跑
I need to do the shuttle run in under 35 seconds.
哦  你想让我来训练你
Oh, so you want me to train you?
- 我很乐意  - 其实  我想让你当枪手来替我跑
- I'd be happy to. - Actually, I was thinking you'd do it for me.
我给你戴副眼镜
I'd give you some glasses.
穿上古怪的筒形袜
Some fancy tube socks.
乔伊  无意冒犯  但是没人会认为我就是你的
Joey, no offense, but no one's going to believe that I'm you.
你猜怎么着  你说的很对
You know what... you're right.
为何我天生就这么帅气啊
Why did I have to be born so handsome?